topaix.com 2011-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Topaix.com

### PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

This Privacy Policy has been established to explain how your information is collected, used and protected with Topaix.com (the Site). This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice.

**PRIVACY PROTECTION**  
The Site does not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other similar sites. The Site recommends its customers to keep their password safe. The Site, or persons who post on the Site, may provide links to third party websites, with different privacy policies. The Site is not responsible for, nor have any control over, those third party websites. The Site does not control third party privacy policies and can't be held accountable for their services/contents/use. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
The Site uses registration form that requires users to provide us contact information (such as name and email address) and other information that is used by us to provide services. We use the customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information that he or she has requested regarding the Site or regarding services offered by us. This Site uses an ad form for customers to place online classified ads.

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
The Site may disclose information about its users in following situations:  
\- By publishing ads online in connection with items that are for sale by customers,  
\- If required by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process,  
\- If required by law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to - enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-party; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Site, its users or the general public.

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**  
We may use your IP address to identify you, your membership, or gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose server problems, and administer the Site. The Site also uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

**OPT-OUT**  
If you wish to opt-out of receiving communications from us, or remove your information from our database or elect to no loner receive services from us, please contact us.

**GLOBAL USE**  
By visiting the Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the global use of the Site we may use the data collected in the course of your use of our site and/or services for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications to you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Data provided to us may be stored on servers throughout different jurisdictions. User agrees to consent to transfer of such data to different locations.

**CONTACT US**  
You can contact us if you have any questions about this privacy policy, or any other issues at info [at] topaix.com.
